export default [
{
        id: 0,
        question: 'What is 10 + 0 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['39','33','36','24'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 1,
        question: 'What is 15 + 7 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['27','24','30','35'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 2,
        question: 'What is 10 + 2 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['26','23','32','29'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is 19 + 3 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['35','38','35','41'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 4,
        question: 'What is 11 + 1 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['44','23','41','47'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 5,
        question: 'What is 19 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['27','24','30','37'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is 17 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','31','34','40'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 7,
        question: 'What is 19 + 8 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['32','37','26','29'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 8,
        question: 'What is 11 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['29','32','35','29'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is 18 + 3 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['36','33','42','39'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 10,
        question: 'What is 14 + 4 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['26','32','29','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 11,
        question: 'What is 17 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','28','35'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 12,
        question: 'What is 13 + 0 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','25','32','38'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 13,
        question: 'What is 15 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','29','33','27'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 14,
        question: 'What is 19 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['31','35','28','34'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 15,
        question: 'What is 18 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['37','33','39','36'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 16,
        question: 'What is 10 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','23','28'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 17,
        question: 'What is 13 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['42','36','39','34'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 18,
        question: 'What is 13 + 7 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['34','38','41','44'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 19,
        question: 'What is 10 + 7 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['31','27','28','25'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 20,
        question: 'What is 15 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['34','40','28','37'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 21,
        question: 'What is 15 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','33','32'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 22,
        question: 'What is 10 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['29','26','27','32'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 23,
        question: 'What is 19 + 8 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['37','30','33','27'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 24,
        question: 'What is 17 + 4 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','38','35','32'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 25,
        question: 'What is 11 + 2 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['33','26','39','36'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 26,
        question: 'What is 18 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['32','38','35','34'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 27,
        question: 'What is 17 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','38','41','36'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 28,
        question: 'What is 11 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['39','24','36','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 29,
        question: 'What is 12 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['41','35','38','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 30,
        question: 'What is 16 + 9 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['33','30','36','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 31,
        question: 'What is 18 + 0 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['40','37','34','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 32,
        question: 'What is 17 + 3 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['32','37','43','40'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 33,
        question: 'What is 12 + 3 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['30','28','27','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 34,
        question: 'What is 11 + 9 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['29','30','26','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 35,
        question: 'What is 17 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['31','34','34','28'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 36,
        question: 'What is 12 + 9 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['38','41','32','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 37,
        question: 'What is 15 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['35','29','29','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 38,
        question: 'What is 10 + 6 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['30','29','35','32'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 39,
        question: 'What is 13 + 5 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['28','31','37','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 40,
        question: 'What is 14 + 6 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['32','29','35','34'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 41,
        question: 'What is 15 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['29','34','35','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 42,
        question: 'What is 18 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['28','31','34','37'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 43,
        question: 'What is 16 + 4 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['32','38','31','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 44,
        question: 'What is 15 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','34','29','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 45,
        question: 'What is 13 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['36','33','29','30'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 46,
        question: 'What is 19 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','44','36','41'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 47,
        question: 'What is 12 + 6 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['44','47','28','41'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 48,
        question: 'What is 11 + 1 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','25','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 49,
        question: 'What is 18 + 8 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['39','29','26','32'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 50,
        question: 'What is 19 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['43','46','40','37'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 51,
        question: 'What is 17 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','32','35','36'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 52,
        question: 'What is 16 + 6 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','29','33'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 53,
        question: 'What is 12 + 3 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['28','37','40','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 54,
        question: 'What is 19 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['41','42','38','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 55,
        question: 'What is 15 + 1 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['31','30','34','37'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 56,
        question: 'What is 18 + 6 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['30','36','33','34'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 57,
        question: 'What is 18 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['22','37','25','28'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 58,
        question: 'What is 12 + 1 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['36','33','30','23'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 59,
        question: 'What is 12 + 3 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['29','32','28','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 60,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['37','31','34','25'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 61,
        question: 'What is 13 + 8 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['37','31','43','40'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 62,
        question: 'What is 14 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['24','33','30','27'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 63,
        question: 'What is 13 + 5 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['29','30','35','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 64,
        question: 'What is 12 + 7 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['30','36','32','33'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 65,
        question: 'What is 17 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['39','34','36','42'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 66,
        question: 'What is 13 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['47','41','44','32'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 67,
        question: 'What is 11 + 9 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['30','27','33','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 68,
        question: 'What is 12 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['38','41','44','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 69,
        question: 'What is 16 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','34','39'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 70,
        question: 'What is 16 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['28','32','34','31'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 71,
        question: 'What is 18 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['34','29','35','32'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 72,
        question: 'What is 16 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','37','32','38'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 73,
        question: 'What is 11 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['33','39','30','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 74,
        question: 'What is 17 + 2 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['38','30','35','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 75,
        question: 'What is 11 + 0 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['22','38','32','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 76,
        question: 'What is 12 + 8 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['30','38','32','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 77,
        question: 'What is 15 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['27','28','30','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 78,
        question: 'What is 15 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','34','38'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 79,
        question: 'What is 12 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['41','38','35','29'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 80,
        question: 'What is 11 + 7 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['32','38','31','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 81,
        question: 'What is 10 + 2 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['42','45','39','22'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 82,
        question: 'What is 10 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['29','32','35','33'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 83,
        question: 'What is 12 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['25','26','28','31'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 84,
        question: 'What is 18 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['36','33','37','30'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 85,
        question: 'What is 16 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['28','34','31','34'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 86,
        question: 'What is 19 + 0 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['33','35','32','29'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 87,
        question: 'What is 11 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['38','30','32','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 88,
        question: 'What is 14 + 9 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['39','36','36','42'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 89,
        question: 'What is 10 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['33','38','32','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 90,
        question: 'What is 13 + 7 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['33','39','34','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 91,
        question: 'What is 11 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['28','34','31','31'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 92,
        question: 'What is 14 + 1 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['45','25','39','42'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 93,
        question: 'What is 17 + 1 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['30','27','33','29'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 94,
        question: 'What is 16 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['41','35','38','39'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 95,
        question: 'What is 11 + 0 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['39','42','25','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 96,
        question: 'What is 14 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['31','25','28','28'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 97,
        question: 'What is 15 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['31','34','31','37'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 98,
        question: 'What is 11 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','32','29','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 99,
        question: 'What is 11 + 6 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['38','32','28','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 100,
        question: 'What is 17 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','30','33'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 101,
        question: 'What is 18 + 2 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['40','43','46','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 102,
        question: 'What is 16 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['26','36','33','30'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 103,
        question: 'What is 16 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','36','33','29'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 104,
        question: 'What is 19 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['36','39','32','33'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 105,
        question: 'What is 16 + 9 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['39','38','33','36'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 106,
        question: 'What is 11 + 2 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['23','23','26','29'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 107,
        question: 'What is 19 + 1 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['30','26','29','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 108,
        question: 'What is 17 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','31','34','35'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 109,
        question: 'What is 13 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['31','29','32','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 110,
        question: 'What is 17 + 1 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','28','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 111,
        question: 'What is 12 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['29','26','26','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 112,
        question: 'What is 19 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['39','42','45','40'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 113,
        question: 'What is 10 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['44','41','26','38'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 114,
        question: 'What is 17 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['33','38','32','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 115,
        question: 'What is 17 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['27','30','35','33'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 116,
        question: 'What is 18 + 2 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['29','32','30','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 117,
        question: 'What is 11 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['36','30','30','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 118,
        question: 'What is 19 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['37','39','34','31'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 119,
        question: 'What is 17 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['39','33','42','45'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 120,
        question: 'What is 11 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['37','34','40','25'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 121,
        question: 'What is 16 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['40','35','43','46'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 122,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['45','26','39','42'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 123,
        question: 'What is 12 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['37','40','43','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 124,
        question: 'What is 10 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['29','30','35','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 125,
        question: 'What is 18 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','41','37'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 126,
        question: 'What is 18 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['31','38','44','41'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 127,
        question: 'What is 10 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','27','35','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 128,
        question: 'What is 11 + 1 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['43','40','37','23'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 129,
        question: 'What is 16 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['36','33','30','39'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 130,
        question: 'What is 18 + 4 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['32','36','29','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 131,
        question: 'What is 10 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','33','41','38'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 132,
        question: 'What is 19 + 4 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['32','37','38','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 133,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['40','28','34','37'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 134,
        question: 'What is 14 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['28','34','33','31'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 135,
        question: 'What is 13 + 3 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['37','31','34','28'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 136,
        question: 'What is 15 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['39','36','36','42'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 137,
        question: 'What is 14 + 3 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['41','29','35','38'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 138,
        question: 'What is 11 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['39','36','29','33'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 139,
        question: 'What is 14 + 6 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['42','39','30','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 140,
        question: 'What is 10 + 5 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['32','29','26','25'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 141,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['27','41','35','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 142,
        question: 'What is 19 + 1 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','29','34','32'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 143,
        question: 'What is 12 + 9 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['30','31','27','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 144,
        question: 'What is 13 + 6 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['29','35','32','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 145,
        question: 'What is 12 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['31','40','37','43'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 146,
        question: 'What is 15 + 1 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['41','38','27','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 147,
        question: 'What is 16 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['38','44','34','41'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 148,
        question: 'What is 15 + 4 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['39','36','42','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 149,
        question: 'What is 17 + 1 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','28','41'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 150,
        question: 'What is 18 + 1 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','32','32'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 151,
        question: 'What is 14 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','33','36'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 152,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['35','41','24','38'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 153,
        question: 'What is 19 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','31','34','35'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 154,
        question: 'What is 17 + 1 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['31','37','31','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 155,
        question: 'What is 18 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','29','26'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 156,
        question: 'What is 14 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','38','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 157,
        question: 'What is 17 + 1 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['46','40','32','43'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 158,
        question: 'What is 19 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['40','37','40','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 159,
        question: 'What is 10 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['29','20','32','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 160,
        question: 'What is 17 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['31','32','35','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 161,
        question: 'What is 18 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['27','37','30','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 162,
        question: 'What is 11 + 0 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['41','38','25','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 163,
        question: 'What is 11 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','41','38','24'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 164,
        question: 'What is 14 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['32','38','32','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 165,
        question: 'What is 16 + 9 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['29','38','35','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 166,
        question: 'What is 17 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['42','39','36','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 167,
        question: 'What is 14 + 5 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['43','37','29','40'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 168,
        question: 'What is 14 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','28','33'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 169,
        question: 'What is 11 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['34','38','41','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 170,
        question: 'What is 11 + 5 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['28','28','34','31'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 171,
        question: 'What is 18 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['36','32','39','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 172,
        question: 'What is 14 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['27','26','29','23'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 173,
        question: 'What is 16 + 6 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['26','32','36','29'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 174,
        question: 'What is 18 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['38','32','35','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 175,
        question: 'What is 11 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','27','32','29'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 176,
        question: 'What is 17 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['30','27','31','33'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 177,
        question: 'What is 18 + 9 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['37','37','34','31'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 178,
        question: 'What is 12 + 8 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','34','34','31'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 179,
        question: 'What is 19 + 6 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['37','35','31','34'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 180,
        question: 'What is 15 + 5 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','29','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 181,
        question: 'What is 11 + 5 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['37','43','40','26'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 182,
        question: 'What is 16 + 6 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['37','34','32','40'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 183,
        question: 'What is 17 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['31','34','37','34'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 184,
        question: 'What is 15 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['45','32','39','42'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 185,
        question: 'What is 12 + 8 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','34','29'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 186,
        question: 'What is 13 + 8 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['31','35','28','34'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 187,
        question: 'What is 17 + 6 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['30','37','33','36'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 188,
        question: 'What is 16 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','39','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 189,
        question: 'What is 19 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['29','35','32','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 190,
        question: 'What is 18 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['36','42','36','39'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 191,
        question: 'What is 16 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','25','32','31'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 192,
        question: 'What is 17 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['28','35','31','25'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 193,
        question: 'What is 12 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['33','27','25','30'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 194,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['25','37','31','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 195,
        question: 'What is 11 + 8 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','32','38'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 196,
        question: 'What is 16 + 6 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['32','42','45','48'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 197,
        question: 'What is 13 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['26','32','38','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 198,
        question: 'What is 19 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['38','32','41','44'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 199,
        question: 'What is 12 + 5 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['36','30','29','33'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 200,
        question: 'What is 17 + 0 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['31','30','33','27'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 201,
        question: 'What is 18 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['36','34','33','39'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 202,
        question: 'What is 11 + 9 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['27','30','33','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 203,
        question: 'What is 19 + 7 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['40','40','37','43'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 204,
        question: 'What is 19 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['24','30','27','32'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 205,
        question: 'What is 16 + 9 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['31','37','34','36'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 206,
        question: 'What is 17 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['28','34','31','31'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 207,
        question: 'What is 17 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['40','43','38','37'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 208,
        question: 'What is 12 + 5 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['27','30','36','33'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 209,
        question: 'What is 12 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['43','33','46','40'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 210,
        question: 'What is 13 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['38','31','32','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 211,
        question: 'What is 12 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','28','31'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 212,
        question: 'What is 17 + 1 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['25','28','31','31'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 213,
        question: 'What is 16 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['39','42','36','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 214,
        question: 'What is 18 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['32','42','45','39'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 215,
        question: 'What is 12 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['33','39','29','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 216,
        question: 'What is 12 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['39','28','36','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 217,
        question: 'What is 17 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','35','29'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 218,
        question: 'What is 16 + 7 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['38','33','32','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 219,
        question: 'What is 11 + 5 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['45','26','39','42'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 220,
        question: 'What is 16 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','35','39'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 221,
        question: 'What is 11 + 2 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['34','28','31','26'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 222,
        question: 'What is 15 + 9 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['37','40','34','34'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 223,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','32','26'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 224,
        question: 'What is 19 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['36','30','33','32'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 225,
        question: 'What is 10 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','27','41','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 226,
        question: 'What is 15 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['32','36','33','30'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 227,
        question: 'What is 18 + 0 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['29','32','35','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 228,
        question: 'What is 19 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['26','36','32','29'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 229,
        question: 'What is 17 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['34','35','32','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 230,
        question: 'What is 18 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['34','41','44','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 231,
        question: 'What is 11 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['33','27','30','21'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 232,
        question: 'What is 13 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['33','32','39','36'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 233,
        question: 'What is 14 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['39','45','42','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 234,
        question: 'What is 17 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['40','34','35','37'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 235,
        question: 'What is 14 + 5 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','31','27','24'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 236,
        question: 'What is 10 + 6 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['40','26','34','37'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 237,
        question: 'What is 12 + 6 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['33','39','36','29'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 238,
        question: 'What is 13 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','27','30'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 239,
        question: 'What is 14 + 4 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','39','29'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 240,
        question: 'What is 11 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['21','22','28','25'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 241,
        question: 'What is 12 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','26','27'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 242,
        question: 'What is 18 + 7 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['39','38','33','36'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 243,
        question: 'What is 18 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['34','37','31','31'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 244,
        question: 'What is 10 + 4 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','41','35','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 245,
        question: 'What is 18 + 6 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','38','41'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 246,
        question: 'What is 15 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','33','39','36'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 247,
        question: 'What is 13 + 2 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['28','37','40','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 248,
        question: 'What is 14 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['31','49','43','46'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 249,
        question: 'What is 19 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['37','35','40','43'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 250,
        question: 'What is 10 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','23','38','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 251,
        question: 'What is 18 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['36','36','33','39'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 252,
        question: 'What is 13 + 8 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','35','25','31'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 253,
        question: 'What is 15 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','38','29'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 254,
        question: 'What is 19 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['42','32','26','29'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 255,
        question: 'What is 14 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['27','30','24','30'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 256,
        question: 'What is 12 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['37','31','28','34'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 257,
        question: 'What is 12 + 0 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['24','33','36','30'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 258,
        question: 'What is 12 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['41','44','26','38'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 259,
        question: 'What is 14 + 8 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','37','35'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 260,
        question: 'What is 15 + 1 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['37','40','26','34'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 261,
        question: 'What is 19 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['38','36','35','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 262,
        question: 'What is 13 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['39','33','33','36'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 263,
        question: 'What is 14 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['32','38','35','32'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 264,
        question: 'What is 12 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['32','29','30','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 265,
        question: 'What is 14 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['33','28','25','31'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 266,
        question: 'What is 10 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','29','41','38'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 267,
        question: 'What is 18 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['36','30','33','37'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 268,
        question: 'What is 16 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','39','30'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 269,
        question: 'What is 14 + 4 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['42','39','29','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 270,
        question: 'What is 10 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['41','24','38','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 271,
        question: 'What is 18 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['34','40','37','38'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 272,
        question: 'What is 12 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','27','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 273,
        question: 'What is 12 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['38','28','35','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 274,
        question: 'What is 17 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','27','35'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 275,
        question: 'What is 11 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['36','39','21','42'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 276,
        question: 'What is 12 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','29','34','40'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 277,
        question: 'What is 11 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['34','40','25','37'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 278,
        question: 'What is 18 + 3 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['42','33','39','45'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 279,
        question: 'What is 11 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['30','46','43','40'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 280,
        question: 'What is 13 + 7 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['39','33','42','36'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 281,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['33','39','36','25'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 282,
        question: 'What is 16 + 2 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','34','31','40'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 283,
        question: 'What is 18 + 9 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['25','37','28','31'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 284,
        question: 'What is 16 + 3 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['32','29','38','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 285,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['32','28','35','29'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 286,
        question: 'What is 14 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['32','38','32','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 287,
        question: 'What is 17 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['31','28','34','35'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 288,
        question: 'What is 14 + 3 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['40','43','37','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 289,
        question: 'What is 12 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['28','37','40','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 290,
        question: 'What is 18 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['35','27','24','30'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 291,
        question: 'What is 14 + 9 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['38','34','35','32'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 292,
        question: 'What is 18 + 5 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','35','33','27'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 293,
        question: 'What is 15 + 3 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['28','39','45','42'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 294,
        question: 'What is 15 + 2 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['34','37','28','31'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 295,
        question: 'What is 14 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['33','30','28','27'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 296,
        question: 'What is 14 + 1 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['26','36','39','33'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 297,
        question: 'What is 17 + 7 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','38','38'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 298,
        question: 'What is 19 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','33','27'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 299,
        question: 'What is 15 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','38','34','41'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 300,
        question: 'What is 11 + 6 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['40','43','31','37'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 301,
        question: 'What is 10 + 6 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['25','28','31','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 302,
        question: 'What is 19 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['36','33','39','38'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 303,
        question: 'What is 12 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['23','26','28','29'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 304,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['30','27','33','25'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 305,
        question: 'What is 18 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['24','27','34','30'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 306,
        question: 'What is 11 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['25','33','30','27'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 307,
        question: 'What is 18 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['36','33','37','39'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 308,
        question: 'What is 16 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['29','45','42','39'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 309,
        question: 'What is 14 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['32','44','41','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 310,
        question: 'What is 16 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['30','35','32','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 311,
        question: 'What is 10 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['28','31','27','25'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 312,
        question: 'What is 18 + 5 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['40','37','35','34'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 313,
        question: 'What is 17 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','28','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 314,
        question: 'What is 18 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','37','37'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 315,
        question: 'What is 10 + 1 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['37','40','25','43'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 316,
        question: 'What is 15 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','35','30'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 317,
        question: 'What is 15 + 3 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['32','29','31','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 318,
        question: 'What is 19 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['28','38','31','34'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 319,
        question: 'What is 15 + 9 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','36','39','42'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 320,
        question: 'What is 16 + 1 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['43','40','27','46'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 321,
        question: 'What is 17 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','34','34','31'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 322,
        question: 'What is 15 + 7 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['32','49','46','43'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 323,
        question: 'What is 17 + 8 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['31','28','35','25'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 324,
        question: 'What is 14 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['32','29','32','26'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 325,
        question: 'What is 19 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','38','33'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 326,
        question: 'What is 15 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['33','26','23','29'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 327,
        question: 'What is 17 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['35','39','36','42'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 328,
        question: 'What is 10 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['33','27','33','30'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 329,
        question: 'What is 17 + 1 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','27','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 330,
        question: 'What is 19 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['30','27','24','38'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 331,
        question: 'What is 11 + 9 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['25','30','22','28'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 332,
        question: 'What is 10 + 4 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','30','33','36'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 333,
        question: 'What is 12 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['34','40','37','22'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 334,
        question: 'What is 13 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','36','39'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 335,
        question: 'What is 10 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['29','34','31','37'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 336,
        question: 'What is 14 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['39','33','28','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 337,
        question: 'What is 13 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['49','29','43','46'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 338,
        question: 'What is 15 + 2 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['35','38','27','41'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 339,
        question: 'What is 13 + 7 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['34','37','40','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 340,
        question: 'What is 14 + 4 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['29','37','40','43'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 341,
        question: 'What is 13 + 5 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','32','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 342,
        question: 'What is 16 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['31','34','28','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 343,
        question: 'What is 19 + 0 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['34','37','30','31'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 344,
        question: 'What is 13 + 1 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['28','27','31','34'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 345,
        question: 'What is 14 + 8 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['32','38','35','32'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 346,
        question: 'What is 17 + 8 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['35','44','38','41'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 347,
        question: 'What is 17 + 1 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['29','33','27','30'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 348,
        question: 'What is 12 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','37','32'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 349,
        question: 'What is 13 + 8 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['26','34','23','29'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 350,
        question: 'What is 16 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','39','36'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 351,
        question: 'What is 12 + 2 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['24','37','34','40'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 352,
        question: 'What is 18 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['40','37','37','43'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 353,
        question: 'What is 12 + 3 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','25','32'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 354,
        question: 'What is 12 + 7 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['32','29','26','32'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 355,
        question: 'What is 18 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['31','32','28','34'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 356,
        question: 'What is 13 + 7 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['31','34','34','37'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 357,
        question: 'What is 17 + 2 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['30','35','38','32'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 358,
        question: 'What is 18 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','38','37'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 359,
        question: 'What is 17 + 3 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['32','31','25','28'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 360,
        question: 'What is 17 + 9 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['41','47','36','44'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 361,
        question: 'What is 10 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['39','42','24','45'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 362,
        question: 'What is 10 + 1 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['34','37','24','31'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 363,
        question: 'What is 14 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','40','37','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 364,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','40','27','34'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 365,
        question: 'What is 14 + 8 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['35','32','32','38'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 366,
        question: 'What is 19 + 4 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['46','40','43','37'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 367,
        question: 'What is 15 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['42','39','31','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 368,
        question: 'What is 11 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['26','23','28','29'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 369,
        question: 'What is 16 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['28','31','34','26'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 370,
        question: 'What is 18 + 3 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['32','35','33','38'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 371,
        question: 'What is 17 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['32','29','30','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 372,
        question: 'What is 13 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['36','29','33','39'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 373,
        question: 'What is 13 + 1 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','36','25'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 374,
        question: 'What is 11 + 1 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['22','37','31','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 375,
        question: 'What is 10 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['23','30','33','36'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 376,
        question: 'What is 15 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['31','33','37','34'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 377,
        question: 'What is 15 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['30','29','33','27'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 378,
        question: 'What is 19 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','35','41','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 379,
        question: 'What is 13 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['33','39','36','27'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 380,
        question: 'What is 12 + 1 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['31','28','34','23'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 381,
        question: 'What is 12 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','32','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 382,
        question: 'What is 12 + 1 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['40','43','46','27'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 383,
        question: 'What is 10 + 4 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['32','29','35','28'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 384,
        question: 'What is 11 + 7 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['43','32','40','46'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 385,
        question: 'What is 11 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['42','36','39','27'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 386,
        question: 'What is 13 + 4 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['29','27','32','26'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 387,
        question: 'What is 13 + 3 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['30','32','29','26'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 388,
        question: 'What is 18 + 9 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['35','40','38','41'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 389,
        question: 'What is 18 + 1 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','31','33','25'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 390,
        question: 'What is 16 + 7 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['35','38','32','36'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 391,
        question: 'What is 19 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['33','27','30','36'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 392,
        question: 'What is 16 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['40','37','34','34'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 393,
        question: 'What is 19 + 8 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['37','33','30','27'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 394,
        question: 'What is 19 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['45','42','40','39'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 395,
        question: 'What is 15 + 0 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['29','40','34','37'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 396,
        question: 'What is 15 + 9 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','34','40','37'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 397,
        question: 'What is 12 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['42','30','45','48'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 398,
        question: 'What is 16 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','38','32','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 399,
        question: 'What is 10 + 5 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['40','37','34','25'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 400,
        question: 'What is 12 + 7 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','33','41','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 401,
        question: 'What is 18 + 1 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['30','37','34','40'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 402,
        question: 'What is 17 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['32','36','38','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 403,
        question: 'What is 15 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['35','38','41','34'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 404,
        question: 'What is 16 + 3 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['36','39','42','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 405,
        question: 'What is 19 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','34','28','31'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 406,
        question: 'What is 17 + 0 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['28','26','32','29'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 407,
        question: 'What is 10 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['40','43','30','37'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 408,
        question: 'What is 10 + 2 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['33','23','36','30'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 409,
        question: 'What is 14 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['39','33','31','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 410,
        question: 'What is 11 + 3 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['27','33','36','39'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 411,
        question: 'What is 16 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['45','42','39','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 412,
        question: 'What is 17 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['44','41','38','33'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 413,
        question: 'What is 13 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['47','44','29','41'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 414,
        question: 'What is 19 + 3 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['31','34','32','37'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 415,
        question: 'What is 13 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['29','39','36','33'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 416,
        question: 'What is 19 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','41','29'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 417,
        question: 'What is 10 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','36','33','23'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 418,
        question: 'What is 14 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','29','32','37'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 419,
        question: 'What is 15 + 2 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['30','36','33','39'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 420,
        question: 'What is 13 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['32','35','32','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 421,
        question: 'What is 13 + 4 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['28','32','38','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 422,
        question: 'What is 17 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['33','39','42','36'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 423,
        question: 'What is 14 + 3 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['40','27','34','37'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 424,
        question: 'What is 17 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['32','38','36','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 425,
        question: 'What is 17 + 8 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['37','43','40','37'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 426,
        question: 'What is 18 + 8 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['39','34','31','37'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 427,
        question: 'What is 11 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','34','24','40'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 428,
        question: 'What is 17 + 9 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','39','27'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 429,
        question: 'What is 19 + 7 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','32','38'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 430,
        question: 'What is 18 + 1 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['29','32','31','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 431,
        question: 'What is 18 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['34','40','37','36'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 432,
        question: 'What is 16 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','30','35'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 433,
        question: 'What is 19 + 9 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['33','39','41','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 434,
        question: 'What is 13 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['34','36','30','33'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 435,
        question: 'What is 17 + 0 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','29','33','27'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 436,
        question: 'What is 10 + 1 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['31','24','34','28'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 437,
        question: 'What is 19 + 1 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','33','34','40'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 438,
        question: 'What is 10 + 6 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['39','28','36','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 439,
        question: 'What is 14 + 8 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['36','31','25','28'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 440,
        question: 'What is 19 + 3 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','32','37'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 441,
        question: 'What is 10 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['24','30','27','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 442,
        question: 'What is 16 + 7 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['34','31','33','28'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 443,
        question: 'What is 13 + 2 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['43','26','40','46'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 444,
        question: 'What is 13 + 1 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['39','33','28','36'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 445,
        question: 'What is 17 + 8 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['39','34','28','31'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 446,
        question: 'What is 15 + 5 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['30','35','38','41'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 447,
        question: 'What is 19 + 0 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['34','37','29','31'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 448,
        question: 'What is 16 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['40','32','34','37'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 449,
        question: 'What is 16 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','32','35','35'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 450,
        question: 'What is 19 + 4 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['35','33','36','30'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 451,
        question: 'What is 17 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['39','36','40','42'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 452,
        question: 'What is 11 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['28','30','31','25'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 453,
        question: 'What is 13 + 1 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['28','30','27','33'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 454,
        question: 'What is 11 + 6 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['28','28','31','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 455,
        question: 'What is 14 + 2 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['27','30','24','27'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 456,
        question: 'What is 13 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['34','37','31','29'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 457,
        question: 'What is 17 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['36','39','45','42'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 458,
        question: 'What is 13 + 5 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['30','30','33','27'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 459,
        question: 'What is 15 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','34','35','41'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 460,
        question: 'What is 18 + 7 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['35','41','38','38'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 461,
        question: 'What is 18 + 4 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['33','33','36','30'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 462,
        question: 'What is 11 + 7 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['33','28','27','30'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 463,
        question: 'What is 19 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','36','30','33'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 464,
        question: 'What is 11 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['30','47','41','44'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 465,
        question: 'What is 11 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['30','40','37','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 466,
        question: 'What is 18 + 0 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['40','29','37','43'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 467,
        question: 'What is 16 + 0 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['27','41','38','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 468,
        question: 'What is 12 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['28','32','26','29'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 469,
        question: 'What is 18 + 7 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['36','40','37','43'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 470,
        question: 'What is 15 + 9 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['30','27','24','38'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 471,
        question: 'What is 13 + 9 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['34','29','35','32'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 472,
        question: 'What is 19 + 5 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['41','35','35','38'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 473,
        question: 'What is 12 + 7 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['32','26','33','29'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 474,
        question: 'What is 10 + 9 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['29','40','34','37'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 475,
        question: 'What is 14 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','32','35','33'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 476,
        question: 'What is 12 + 0 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['35','29','32','26'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 477,
        question: 'What is 14 + 1 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['26','33','39','36'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 478,
        question: 'What is 18 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['31','28','25','34'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 479,
        question: 'What is 15 + 0 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['32','27','38','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 480,
        question: 'What is 14 + 7 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['41','44','38','31'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 481,
        question: 'What is 17 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','34','31','36'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 482,
        question: 'What is 19 + 5 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','32','38','35'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 483,
        question: 'What is 17 + 6 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['37','40','43','37'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 484,
        question: 'What is 14 + 3 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['30','33','30','36'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 485,
        question: 'What is 17 + 6 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['37','36','34','31'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 486,
        question: 'What is 12 + 3 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['38','26','32','35'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 487,
        question: 'What is 15 + 8 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['40','34','37','43'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 488,
        question: 'What is 14 + 0 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['27','37','31','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 489,
        question: 'What is 10 + 9 + 11 ?',
        answers: ['45','39','42','30'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 490,
        question: 'What is 18 + 5 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','39','36'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 491,
        question: 'What is 12 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','32','28'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 492,
        question: 'What is 16 + 8 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['37','40','43','38'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 493,
        question: 'What is 15 + 2 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['39','31','36','33'],
        correct: 2

    },
{
        id: 494,
        question: 'What is 12 + 8 + 10 ?',
        answers: ['38','35','30','32'],
        correct: 3

    },
{
        id: 495,
        question: 'What is 13 + 8 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['27','30','33','35'],
        correct: 4

    },
{
        id: 496,
        question: 'What is 19 + 0 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['33','34','37','40'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 497,
        question: 'What is 14 + 2 + 12 ?',
        answers: ['28','31','37','34'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 498,
        question: 'What is 15 + 4 + 14 ?',
        answers: ['33','28','25','31'],
        correct: 1

    },
{
        id: 499,
        question: 'What is 16 + 4 + 13 ?',
        answers: ['33','36','33','30'],
        correct: 1

    },
]
